ADAPTED FROM DEMON KING
OF JINJIANG LITERATURE CITY
ORIGINAL WORK BY JIULU FEIXIANG
I asked around.
Up ahead is Changyue Lane,
where mortals drink flower wine.
Since we want to be mortals,
we can't miss this fun activity.
What does drinking flower wine mean?
The flower refers to a woman.
Drinking flower wine
means going to a brothel
and finding a beautiful lady
to sing for and entertain us.
I don't think it's a good idea.
Indulging in pleasure will bungle matters.
Bungle matters?
What matters?
We came to Lucheng for relaxation.
Didn't we?
That's right.
Exactly.
See? The master has given the order.
Our top priority today is to have fun.
We're drinking our way
down the street today.
Let's get hammered!
Guests, please head on in.
Please come in.
- Please enter.
- Bravo.
Let's go over there.
- Go over there.
- Please come in.
Sir.
What is this place?
This is Flying Immortal Pavilion,
where Lady Wanqing lives.
Don't you know?
We just arrived in Lucheng.
Who is Lady Wanqing?
She is the most beautiful courtesan
on Changyue Lane in Lucheng.
Her mastery of the Six Arts
is unmatched in the world.
She is even
as beautiful as the fairies in heaven.
No, she is even more beautiful.
Have you seen
the fairies in heaven?
I'm not talking nonsense.
Lady Wanqing came to Changyue Lane
at the age of 15.
Her magnificent dance
made a hundred flowers bloom.
Word of it spread all over Lucheng.
Even the children knew.
It sounds like
Lady Wanqing is indeed
a reincarnation of a fairy.
But now,
only noble families
have the privilege of seeing Lady Wanqing.
Ordinary folk like us will never see her.
If I'm lucky enough
to see her dance again,
I shall die without regret.
In that case, I am determined
to meet her today.
Look.
That is Lady Wanqing's floral invitation.
Only by having that
can you enter Flying Immortal Pavilion.
Young man, please halt.
We heard that Lady Wanqing
is versatile and gorgeous.
We came from afar to visit her.
Do you have a floral invitation?
No.
But will this be enough
to meet Lady Wanqing?
You underestimate our lady.
Flying Immortal Pavilion has its rules.
Please don't make my job difficult.
That's too much.
You're giving too much.
Please come in.
- Please enter.
TOO ELATED TO WORRY
- Welcome, sir.
- Sir, please drink slowly.
- Nice to meet you.
- I'll pour you another glass.
Sir.
You're a sweet talker.
Come.
- Come on.
- You are here too.
Lord Changheng?
Why is he in Lucheng too?
No. I don't detect
an Immortal Pond in him.
He seems to be a mortal.
Why does he look
exactly like Lord Changheng?
A Magical Firefly Stone?
He is Lord Changheng.
Is he also experiencing tribulations
in the Mortal World?
- Come.
- This is bad.
If Dongfang Qingcang finds out,
he will kill him,
making him fail his tribulation
and he'll dissipate.
Mr. Dongfang!
Mr. Dongfang.
Why don't we sit here?
We can have a clearer view here.
Lady Wanqing is coming.
- Hurry.
- Come on.
- Let's go and see.
- Let's go and have a look.
- Goodness.
- Yes.
It's her.
It's starting.
Why is there a Hellfire mark
on Xie Wanqing?
Thirty thousand years of tribulations.
The high immortal who was injured
by Hellfire 30,000 years ago.
Xie Wanqing is the reincarnation
of the former God of War.
It seems he already knew.
What does he want to do
with her primordial spirit?
No matter what he wants to do,
I must stop him
and protect the former God of War.
This dance is so beautiful.
But you seem absent-minded.
Something seems to be on your mind.
There isn't.
What kind of dance is this?
It's so beautiful.
What about you?
Would you like to tell me
what is on your mind?
I…
Bravo!
What's wrong?
I think I ate something bad today.
Do you have a stomachache?
I was wondering who it was.
- It's the devil incarnate.
- Yes.
Who is he?
Xiao Run,
the second son of the Xiao family.
He's the top playboy in Lucheng.
He is ignorant
and indulges in pleasure all day.
He isn't qualified to be here.
Uncouth as he is,
he can only crassly shout praises.
How can he understand
the intricacies of the dance?
So
Lord Changheng is called Xiao Run
in this life.
Mr. Wang presents Lady Wanqing
with 5,000 taels of gold!
Five thousand taels.
Mr. Su of Cloud Weaving Atelier presents
ten rolls of light cyan fabric,
ten rolls of cloud-patterned brocade,
and ten rolls
of landscape-patterned brocade.
Minister Li from the Ministry of Revenue
presents a case of jewelry.
Jieli, what are you doing?
Why are you so excited?
It's money, Orchid.
Do you know how much those are worth?
Do you have any use
for money in the Mortal World?
Of course.
When I look at gold and jewelry,
I feel bright-eyed and refreshed.
I would sleep incredibly soundly
on a bed of gold.
Mr. Xiao presents an imperial...
An imperial gift of a red coral tree!
- Imperial gift?
- Is there such a thing?
- Amazing.
- Goodness.
How lucky.
An imperial gift?
An imperial gift.
It's from the emperor.
Do you know who that is?
He is the equivalent
of the Moon Supreme in Yunmeng Lake.
That is a unique and priceless treasure.
Mr. Xiao presented a priceless treasure.
No one can match him.
So he can be Lady Wanqing's guest.
I have to see
who Mr. Xiao is.
Mr. Xiao, this way, please.
Thank you.
I can't believe he can simply give away
an imperial gift.
My goodness.
What now?
The Bone Orchid is missing.
What?
I was wearing it just now.
I don't know why it is suddenly gone.
Don't worry.
The Bone Orchid obeys my orders.
I will summon it now.
No, don't.
Don't use any powers.
Have you forgotten?
Mortal lives are destined.
We can't disturb them.
Otherwise,
these mortals will turn into ashes.
Shangque, help me find it.
Search.
Yes.
You must help me find it
because Bone Orchid
is priceless to me.
I found it.
Why exactly did you come to Yunmeng Lake?
I…
I'm here to accompany you.
FLYING IMMORTAL PAVILION
Mr. Xiao.
Hi, Lady Wanqing.
Who is this monkey?
No descendant of the nobility in Lucheng
dares to be so rude to our lady.
My lady, I'm Xiao Run.
We met at Xiao Mansion
when we were just children.
Do you remember?
No.
Our fathers were classmates
and also officials in the same court.
The late emperor even betrothed you to me
before birth.
Do you remember this?
Ten years ago,
my father fell victim to a political feud.
In the Xie family,
men were exiled
to the harsh northern frontiers
and women were forced
to be courtesans in the Royal Academy.
I'm a convicted person.
You need not mention
our engagement ever again.
My lady, you're wrong.
Although the Xiao family
and Xie family have changed,
a gentleman must keep his promise.
Since we are engaged,
I can't break my promise.
I came with an imperial gift
of a red coral tree
to propose to you today.
Wanqing.
Why don't you agree
to such a good marriage?
His father
has a successful official career.
His brother is a top scholar
and highly favored by the emperor.
You're lucky
to receive this offer from Xiao Run.
If you say yes,
you will enjoy a life of luxury.
Must I say yes just because he wants me?
This playboy wants
to play this game of courtship,
but he doesn't know
that my heart has never been in this game.
I'm not like him.
Wanqing,
given your current status,
how can you still be so picky
like a daughter of nobility?
Forget about a wealthy family
like the Xiaos.
You won't even get to be an official wife
in any respectable family.
Listen to me.
You're not young anymore.
I've gone through this.
In this field,
everyone prefers the new over the old.
Others consider this a great favor.
But in my opinion,
I will just be living in another cage.
Tongyun.
Mr. Xiao,
this cup of tea
is all that will come of us.
I thank you for your favor.
Please leave.
Since you don't want to say yes today,
I'll come another day.
This man.
Mr. Xiao.
My lady brewed this tea herself.
He just gulped it down.
He really is uncouth.
Tongyun.
Return the imperial red coral tree
to Mr. Xiao.
My dear.
Go now.
If you really refuse this marriage,
you will…
Don't worry, Madam.
I have my own plan.
I already have the best choice in mind.
Is there anyone
better than wealthy Mr. Xiao
that wants to marry you?
- Move. I need to see Mr. Xiao.
- Cricket? Why are you here?
I told you to stay home to do my homework.
Bad news. Master found out.
He lost his temper in the study.
He broke three teacups.
I've skipped lessons before.
Take it easy.
No, it's because of the coral tree.
Come on, let's go.
Be careful.
Let's go. Hurry up.
Once they're gone,
sneak into the backyard
and get Grandmother to save me.
Don't be so clumsy. Be careful.
If my father finds out,
he will kill me.
Do you hear me?
Father.
Beat him.
Gambling and soliciting courtesans.
That's all fine.
Bastard.
Today, you even stole the coral tree
that the emperor bestowed upon me
to solicit those in the pleasure district!
Father, let me explain.
The coral tree sits there daily
and you worship it day and night.
If you continue like that,
you won't be able to straighten your back!
Father, I'm just worried about you.
Stop quibbling.
Father,
Lady Wanqing has returned the coral tree.
How many strikes has it been?
Master, more than 30 times.
Get up!
Go to bed.
Go to school tomorrow morning.
- Be careful.
- Lady Wanqing?
She's just a courtesan.
Father, you can't say that.
Don't say it.
My engagement with her
was arranged by the late emperor.
If I don't fulfill this promise,
I'll be committing high treason.
Bastard!
The late emperor
had merely joked about the engagement.
If you truly do marry her,
the Xiao family
will become a laughingstock in Lucheng!
If everyone in Lucheng learns
that the Xiao family are utter snobs
who judge others based on their status,
then we'll really be a laughingstock.
Every single thing I do
is for our family.
In this world,
you can't find a son
as loyal and filial as me.
Father,
you always taught me
to read the books of sages
and become a scholar like my brother.
If I were to be like you,
well-read yet so hypocritical,
I would rather be an illiterate commoner!
Unfilial son!
- Come here.
- Master, calm down.
- Hit me. I'm tough.
- Come here.
- You won't feel sorry.
- I'll kill you.
Come here. Father.
You two are really close.
If you both want to be punished,
I'll grant you your wish!
As a man, I'll answer for my actions.
Don't hit Cricket.
You have an iron backbone.
From now on,
you won't get a monthly allowance anymore!
Father, I was wrong.
Xiao Run,
letting your father scold you
wouldn't cost you anything.
Why did you say that nonsense
and anger your father?
My father
is always full of hypocritical words.
Look.
He showed his true colors, didn't he?
Xiao Run,
do you really want to marry Lady Wanqing?
You don't even like her.
She is noble-minded and elegant.
The brothel hasn't changed her nature.
She is a hero among women.
I don't have romantic feelings for her,
but I do feel fondness as a friend.
If she agrees,
I will treat her well in the future.
Besides…
Ever since I was young,
I've kept dreaming of a fairy.
She has an ethereal quality,
like an orchid in a remote valley.
She bears similarities to Lady Wanqing.
Do you think
Lady Wanqing and I are destined
to be married?
FLYING IMMORTAL PAVILION
- Take care.
Be careful.
Sir, take care.
What's wrong? Are you still drunk?
No, it's nothing.
After walking all day
without flying,
my legs are sore.
It's not easy to be a mortal.
Why don't I carry you?
No, thank you.
I'm not tired all of a sudden.
It's true.
Jieli.
What are you doing?
My dear Shangque,
I'm tired too.
Carry me too.
Shangque, why are you running?
- By the way--
You go first.
You first.
You said
that there is no love between us.
Then why did you say
that Bone Orchid is priceless to you?
Well…
Are you lying to me?
No.
Then
did you lie
that there is no love between us?
No.
In the future,
if you do attack Shuiyuntian
and kill the fairies,
you will be my enemy.
Then
what were you trying to say just now?
You…
Are you really not angry with me?
Angry?
In the past,
if I had said or done something
to disobey you,
you would have been angry with me
and lost your temper.
"I will kill you."
Is that how I used to treat you?
Yes.
But these days,
I've said things you don't like,
managed you,
and even lost the Bone Orchid.
But you haven't been like before.
Are you really not mad at me?
My lord,
what is on your mind?
You've been sitting here
since you came back.
Do you think
I have been abnormal lately?
You've always been wise.
Nothing is abnormal.
Not that.
I've been distracted recently.
I can't concentrate.
Especially when it comes to Orchid.
Sometimes, I should be angry,
but I can't get angry.
I even hope she will make me angry.
But she…
She always used to talk my ear off.
But now,
she doesn't want
to spend a single second with me.
It has become quiet.
Yet I feel…
Tell me.
What is the matter with me?
Now that you bring it up--
Orchid!
Orchid, wait for me!
I have had the same symptoms recently.
But I don't know
the specific reason.
What?
Xiao Run is Lord Changheng?
Quiet down.
Do you mean the Lord Changheng
that you are always talking about?
Currently, Lord Changheng
is going through tribulation.
Do you remember?
You once asked me
about a high god's tribulation.
Yes.
You said that it is fraught with dangers.
If they fail to complete the tribulation,
they will dissipate.
That's right.
Don't tell anyone about this.
If Dongfang Qingcang finds out,
Lord Changheng will die.
Don't worry. I won't say anything.
But Lord Changheng
should be in Shuiyuntian.
Why is he in the Mortal World?
I don't know.
Maybe it has to do
with the former God of War.
Wait.
Who is the former God of War?
Lady Wanqing, whom we saw today.
I'm guessing she is the former God of War
who sacrificed herself for Shuiyuntian.
This is Lady Chidi's tribulation.
Lady Chidi?
I seem to have heard of this name.
No, wait.
But she died 30,000 years ago.
How is she alive now?
I don't know why.
I only know
that Dongfang Qingcang
might want her primordial spirit.
Why does he want her primordial spirit?
Whatever the reason,
it must be bad for Shuiyuntian.
Jieli, what should we do
if it is true?
Forget it. Don't worry about it.
We'll figure it out later.
Tomorrow is the Lantern Festival.
We should have fun.
The Lantern Festival?
"The night of the Lantern Festival."
"Meeting her beloved."
The night of the Lantern Festival
is when Xie Wanqing will meet
her destined lover.
That is tomorrow night.
Her destined lover.
That's right.
Xiao Run and Xie Wanqing
were engaged to each other.
Today, he even proposed to her.
Her destined lover is Lord Changheng.
SPIRIT-SHATTERING ABYSS, XISHAN
What time is it in Yunmeng Lake now?
You haven't recovered.
Don't act rashly.
It's almost time.
Lantern Festival, Yiyou Year.
I'm going to keep her company.
- Is this the Lantern Festival?
- Is this new to you?
- We need to find Lady Chidi soon.
- It is.
I want to watch her tribulation.
Yes.
There's an acrobatic show.
Let's take a look.
- All right.
- Don't go.
What's so interesting about acrobats?
Let's go and see mortals' magic.
That's right.
We should take a look around
since we are here.
I'll go and explore the way with Shangque.
I'll go too.
Don't.
Why are you leaving?
You stay here.
Shangque and I can explore the way.
- Let's go.
- Jieli.
- Jie…
Come on.
What are you looking at?
Stupid Black Dragon.
You've served him for over 30,000 years.
Why are you still so clueless?
What do you mean?
The Lantern Festival is so lively
with such beautiful sights.
Don't you want the lord
to be alone with Orchid?
But…
Why don't we
spend some time together?
I don't want to be alone with you.
We're exploring the way.
Wait for me.
Why are you leaving?
Stop!
Sir.
Buy a flower.
These freshly-picked lilies and peonies
are all beautiful.
They'll look even better
in the lady's hair.
No, thank you, little girl.
Sir, buy one.
I wish you two
a union lasting a hundred years.
Only a hundred years?
If that is not enough,
then thousands and millions of years.
All right, I'll have one.
Thank you, sir.
Turn around.
All right.
I…
I've just seen men in the Mortal World
adorning women with flowers.
Since we are to pretend to be mortals,
we should act the part.
Sir.
Did you come to Lucheng
just to relax?
Or is there something else?
Nothing else.
Are you lying to me?
No.
I'm just here to relax.
Why do you ask this?
No reason.
I just wanted to ask.
Since you're so worried,
I promise you
I won't lie to you ever again.
But
don't lie to me again either.
All right?
All right.
Cuju balls!
Come and have a look!
Sir, have a look.
Buy one.
Look at my Cuju balls.
Sir, pick one.
Take a look.
Sir.
Pick one.
Come on!
Place your bets.
- Big!
- Small!
- Hurry up!
- Anyone betting on big?
- Big!
- Anyone betting on small?
- Small!
- Big!
Place your bets!
One, two, three! Small!
Mr. Xiao, thank you.
Let's stop here.
That's enough.
Take a break
in the tea room on the second floor.
No.
Let's continue.
If my memory serves me,
you have no more money on you.
Don't keep gambling.
- Or you will be embarrassed.
- Come on, let's continue.
- I'll bet big this time.
- Folks, place your bets!
- Xiao Run, what are you doing?
- Big!
- Cricket.
- How long have you been with me?
- Big.
I lost my parents at a young age.
Since you brought me back,
I've been following you.
It has been at least 11 years.
Over the past decade,
haven't we eaten and slept together?
I'll open it.
Didn't I treat you as my brother?
Didn't I treat you well?
Of course.
Let's continue.
My good brother.
Lend me your allowance from last month.
Any more?
- I'll open it.
- One last time.
It's really the last time.
I'll pay 40% interest.
Any more?
- Any more?
- If not, then 50% interest.
- Here!
- No, Xiao Run.
You…
Don't hesitate. Hurry up.
You're such a slowpoke.
- Take it out.
- Hurry up.
I really can't.
If you don't give it to me,
I'll tell my father
that you took me to go whoring,
gambling, and drinking.
Then he'll break your legs.
Big or small?
Give it to me.
- I won!
- Come on!
Give it to me.
Hurry.
Come on, I'm opening it.
- Four, five, six. Big!
- Make way.
- One more time.
- Big.
Mr. Xiao.
Do you think our gambling house
is for charity?
Take away your spare change.
Don't play if you can't afford it.
How is it not enough?
I have spent a lot
in your gambling house.
The past is the past.
Tonight's stakes
have been accumulated until now.
Your spare change is not enough.
All right.
Go on and bet.
I bet this.
Xiao Run, let's just leave.
Don't bet with the jade!
It's none of your business.
- Yes, it's a bother.
- Is this jade enough?
Yes, it is.
Come on.
Come, place your bets!
- Big or small?
- You can't use the jade!
- Big.
One, two, three. Small!
I gained!
- Thank you, Mr. Xiao.
- Why did you lose again?
Say, you put treasures on the line.
I'll count to three.
Grab it and run.
One, two,
three!
Catch him!
- Don't let him escape!
- Mine!
Don't let him run away!
Let's split up. See you at home.
Catch them!
You've been sitting here all night.
Aren't you going to the lantern market?
It's lively outside.
There are many circuses and lion dancing.
What a racket.
It doesn't interest me.
Then
how about going back and having a rest?
Don't catch a cold.
I'm waiting.
Who are you waiting for?
I don't know.
How long will you wait?
You must be drunk.
My lady,
you've enjoyed the moon and the wine.
Go back and rest.
I've seen everything
in my life.
Precious horses and priceless fur coats.
I've experienced everything in the world.
But I still feel
that I'm waiting for something
that I'm missing.
Are you waiting for the perfect man
who understands you?
I don't know.
My lady.
Let's go back and rest.
This music
is what I've been waiting for.